<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView  xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content">
<FrameLayout
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content">

    <LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
        android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        >
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginLeft="@dimen/text_margin"
            android:layout_marginRight="@dimen/text_margin"
            android:layout_marginTop="45dp"
            android:text="Basic Information:"
            android:textSize="20sp"
            android:paddingTop="10dp"
            android:textColor="@color/primary"
            android:id="@+id/heading"
            />
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginLeft="@dimen/text_margin"
            android:layout_marginRight="@dimen/text_margin"
            android:layout_marginTop="2dp"
            android:text="Getting around Singapore is easy and convenient with the efficient public transportation network which offers taxis, buses and the modern Mass Rapid Transit (MRT) and Light Rail Transit (LRT) rail system.\nTravelling on the MRT is the easiest and most convenient way to get around in Singapore.The comprehensive network across Singapore makes it easy to access all parts of Singapore.\n\nBuses in Singapore are regular and routes are widely covered, leaving nowhere in Singapore inaccessible. Often bus stops or bus interchanges can be found next to MRT stations, which makes the travel journey an efficient one.Fares may be paid by cash or the ez-link card, which can be used for the MRT, public buses and some taxis.\nThe ez-link card is a contactless stored value card. The cost of your journey will be automatically deducted when you alight from the MRT or bus.\nTo purchase this card, you can go to\n  &#8226; Any Transitlink Ticket Office ($12).\n  &#8226; 7-Eleven stores ($10)\n  &#8226; Any SingPost ($5)\n\nTop-up of the ez-link card can be done at\n  &#8226; General Ticketing Machines\n  &#8226; TransitLink Ticket Offices\n  &#8226; TransitLink Add Value Machines\n  &#8226; 7-Eleven stores\n  &#8226; SingPost\n  &#8226; ATMS (DBS/POSB, OCBC)\n  &#8226; AXS Stations\n\nGenerally transportation fares are affordable. For more information and details about bus routes and MRT/LRT routes one can download official Land and Transport Authority app &quot;MyTransport Singapore&quot; available at both Google Play and the iTunes App Store.\n\nGetting around Campus:\nOne can use any of the NUS internal shuttle buses, in their distinctive blue and orange colours to get around campus hassle free.There are four separate NUS Internal Shuttle Bus Services (Service A, Service B, Service C, Service D and BTC service) plying the campus. The four bus services complement one another for wide coverage of the campus.\nFor more information and details about shuttle bus routes,one can download NUS transport app &quot;NUS NextBus&quot; available at both Google Play and the iTunes App Store."
            android:textSize="18sp"
            android:paddingBottom="10dp"
            android:textColor="@color/primary"
            android:id="@+id/basicInfo"
            />
        <View
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="6dp"
            android:background="@color/base"
            android:id="@+id/spacer"/>
    </LinearLayout>
</FrameLayout>
</ScrollView>